总统看到我高潮了
Well, the president just saw me come.
安德伍德竞选总统
-不喜欢我的长颈鹿吗  -不喜欢
- You don't like my giraffe? - No.
你知道我离过两次婚
You know I'm divorced twice
还有个女儿在上大学吧
and have a daughter in college, right?
-你的维基百科页上有  -维基百科
- It's on your Wikipedia page. - Wikipedia.
老天
Christ.
我不指望什么
I don't have any expectations.
我从不指望任何人
I never have, of anyone.
你也不该
You shouldn't either.
我们今天翘了几场活动
How many events have we skipped today?
三场
Three so far.
第四场也要错过了
And we're about to skip a fourth.
-都记在《电讯报》账上  -我是名自由记者
- All on the Telegraph's dime. - Hey, I'm a free agent.
所以我见过成千上万次的
Means I'm free to bail on a speech
陈词滥调我想翘就翘
I've already seen ten thousand times.
没有天生的...
You are entitled...
-福利  -你少来
- to nothing. - Stop.
我说明白了  我觉得...
Let me be clear. I say, I say...
你过来  小子
Come here, boy.
没有天生的...
You are entitled...
福利
To nothing!
事实就是  美国梦破灭了
Now, here's the truth: The American dream is broken.
我们连梦想都被剥夺了
And when we are robbed of our dreams,
告诉我  我们还有什么
well, let me ask you, folks, what are we left with?
一无所有
Nothing!
当我要求国会帮我将这个国家
And when I asked Congress to help me take this country
从福利国家变为充分就业的国家
from a welfare state to a fully-employed nation,
国会有什么行动
what did Congress do?
无动于衷
Nothing!
当我们证明了《美国就业法案》有用
And when we proved that America Works actually works,
安德伍德竞选2016
支持安德伍德
支持就业法案
让美国有工作
在华盛顿创造了五万个岗位
when we created 50,000 jobs in Washington DC,
国会这下有行动了
Congress didn't just stop at nothing,
他们扼杀了进步
they killed progress in its tracks.
相信我  我明白你们的感受
Believe me, I know how you feel.
但我们得记住来这里的目的
But we have to remember why we're here.
我们得把愤怒转化为行动
We have to turn that anger into action.
夫人  杜兰特国务卿
Ma'am, it's Secretary Durant,
-有急事找您  -《美国就业法案》能成功
- she said it's urgent. - America Works will succeed,
但我们需要你们的帮助
but we need your help.
什么事
Hello?
得让他们知道支持弗兰克·安德伍德
You need to let them know that a vote for Frank Underwood
就是支持《美国就业法案》
is a vote for America Works!
支持弗兰克·安德伍德就是支持《美国就业法案》
A vote for Frank Underwood is a vote for America Works!
今早我有幸
Now, I had the great pleasure
结识了一个叫格洛丽亚的姑娘
of meeting a woman this morning named Gloria.
她有爱荷华州立大学学位
She has a degree from Iowa State University
凭她的学历还是找不到工作
and even with her degree, she can't get employed.
为什么  为什么会这样
Now, why? Why is that the case?
因为  我妻子  女士们  先生们
Becau-- My wife, ladies and gentlemen.
八名俄罗斯人在约旦合谷遇难
我觉得我妻子想
I think what my wife is gently
委婉地告诉我  我超时了
trying to tell me is that I've run overtime.
她给我取了个很合适的外号
She has a very clever nickname for me.
-"话唠"  -是啊
- "Verbosity." - Yeah.
克莱尔和我最大的区别
Now, the main difference between Claire and me,
当然除了她的美丽之外
aside from her stunning beauty, of course,
是她真明白这个词的意思
is that she actually knows what that word means.
我很乐意在这里待一个下午
Now, look, I would love to stay here all afternoon
回答你们所有的问题
and answer all your questions,
但那样我就得让
but then I'd leave all your friends
锡达拉皮兹的朋友们等我了
in Cedar Rapids waiting for me
他们已经等很久了  那可不好
even longer than they have and we don't want to do that.
感谢大家今天前来看我
So I want to thank you all for coming out to see me today,
听我讲我们参与的这场斗争
to hear about this battle, this fight we're in.
你们要在党团会议中支持我
I want you to caucus for me,
帮格洛丽亚找到工作
and let's help get Gloria a job!
有你一票  才有《美国就业法案》
America Works only if you make it work!
天佑爱荷华  天佑美利坚合众国
God bless Iowa! God bless the United States of America!
-谢谢  -安德伍德  安德伍德
- Thank you! - Underwood! Underwood! Underwood!
简易爆炸装置  就在90号公路旁
An IED right off Route 90,
距约旦河三千米处
three kilometers from the Jordan River.
-什么时候  -36分钟前
- When? - Thirty-six minutes ago.
一队俄国士兵在巡逻  两辆装甲车被毁
Russian unit was on patrol. Two armored vehicles were destroyed.
-8名士兵全部遇难  -凯茜给谁打电话呢
- All eight troops were killed. - Who's Cathy spoken to?
外交部长仍未回电话
Foreign Minister hasn't returned her call.
我们要确保联合国秘书长保持沉默
We have to make sure the Secretary General doesn't say anything
直至我们能更好地控制事态
until we have a better handle on this.
雷米  我需要立即与佩特罗夫通话
Remy, I need to speak to Petrov immediately.
我联系了克里姆林宫  对方说稍后回话
I contacted the Kremlin. They said he'll reach out soon.
我们需要联合国去调查爆炸地点
We need the UN to investigate the blast site.
俄国人已经拉起警戒线  不让任何人接近
The Russians have cordoned it off. They're not letting anyone in.
-为什么  -我们不清楚
- Why not? - We don't know.
我们有个小队在附近  听到爆炸  想去帮忙
We had a unit nearby that heard the blast, went in to help.
-俄国人拒绝了  -我不喜欢这气氛
- Russians turned them away. - I don't like the feel of this.
凯茜说以色列想派出他们自己的人
Cathy says the Israelis want to send in their own team.
这绝对不行
We can't let that happen.
以色列一到...
The second Israeli boots hit the ground--
雷米  我不管你使什么办法
Remy, I don't care what you have to do,
接通佩特罗夫的电话
you get Petrov on the phone.
我们必须阻止事态酝酿
We need to head this off at the pass.
并确保国会中没人反应过激
And make sure no one in Congress overreacts either.
翻译   肉松富士
翻译   杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译   国士章鱼X
翻译   香茗小焙
翻译   艾瑞卡
翻译   somehacker
翻译   面条打包子
时间轴   Kallen
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
鸣谢   忙成狗的网飞
鸣谢   阿小小海
特效   草草
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第三季  第九集
比赛怎么样
How was the game?
棒极了  直到我手机开始响个不停
Great, until my phone started blowing up.
我看看你写得怎么样了
Let me see what you have so far.
不行
No.
这样不行  语言过于直白
This is no good. The language is too obtuse.
-这样简单  直接  -听着  是这样的
- Simpler. More direct. - Look, here's the deal:
如果俄国不配合  以色列就会紧张
If the Russians don't play ball, the Israelis will get nervous.
如果以色列出兵  巴勒斯坦就会勃然大怒
If the Israelis send troops in, the Palestinians will go apeshit.
如果巴勒斯坦发怒  就可能搬出迫击炮
If the Palestinians go apeshit, there could be mortar attacks.
如果出现那种情况  整个维和行动
And if there are mortar attacks, the whole peacekeeping mission
-就泡汤了  -你想让我就这么写吗
- could go down the drain. - You want me to actually say that?
天啊  当然不  恰恰相反
God, no. We need to say the opposite.
听着  清楚描述一番
Look, make it as clear as
我刚刚形容的末日局势
the doomsday scenario that I just described,
但随后180度转弯  表示无需紧张
but then flip it around and put a happy face on it.
其他的都能重新安排
We can reschedule everything else,
但是我担心哈兰·特劳伯
but I'm concerned about Harlan Traub.
爱荷华民主党主席
The IDP Chairman.
也是食品加工协会的主席
And President of the Food Processors Association.
他在州内很有影响力
He's big for us statewide.
我们本约好今晚与他见面
We were supposed to meet with him tonight.
现在出现了紧急国家安全事务
Well, this is a national security emergency.
他还没与邓巴会面
He hasn't met with Dunbar yet.
如果我们取消  她就能先跟他联系
If we cancel, she gets a clean shot at him.
好吧  那就让他也上飞机
All right, so put him on the plane.
别忘了选举委员会的规则
FEC rules.
在空军一号上拉票每小时花费17.9万
Campaigning on Air Force One costs 179,000 an hour.
-更别提这传出去的影响  -那我不拉票
- Aside from the message it sends-- - Alright. So I won't campaign.
反正我也没时间  让他感到受优待就行
I won't have time anyway. Uh, just make him feel special.
然后安排他在华盛顿跟我见面
Give him some face time in Washington.
怎么样
Anything?
莫里科夫的办公室在搪塞我
Moryakov's office is giving me the runaround.
简易爆炸装置炸死八名
An IED has killed eight Russian troops
八名俄罗斯士兵丧生约旦河谷
在约旦河谷巡逻的俄罗斯士兵
on patrol in the Jordan Valley.
截至目前尚无人声称对此次袭击负责
So far, no one has claimed responsibility for this attack.
克里姆林宫对此的唯一反应是一份来自
The only reaction from the Kremlin, a brief written statement
外交部长布加耶夫的简短声明  援引如下
from Foreign Minister Bugayev that reads, quote,
"袭击者会被绳之以法"  引述完毕
"The perpetrators will be found and brought to justice." End quote.
-20分钟后出发  -我得去我房间拿行李
- Wheels up in 20 minutes. - I gotta grab my bags from my room.
-好的  外面见  -我们该分开搭车
- Okay. Meet me out front. - We should take separate cars.
这种地方  飞机起飞你都打不到车
A cab won't even get here before the plane takes off.
跟我走吧
You're coming with me.
遵命
Yes, sir.
今天不是逃学的好日子
Not a good day to play hooky.
今晚要熬到很晚了
It's gonna be a late night here.
取决于佩特罗夫的行动
It depends what Petrov does.
目前为止  只有刺耳的沉默
So far, just incredibly loud silence.
我得走了  宝贝  外交部要召开紧急会议
I gotta go, hon. Foreign Affairs is holding an emergency session.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
-我时间不多  -我也是
- I don't have much time. - Neither do I.
讲话要点
Talking points.
这让我很不自在
These make me uncomfortable.
即使是非公开会议  我的话也会泄露
Even in a closed session, whatever I say will get out.
-我会因此在爱荷华受挫  -你不能挑剔任务
- I'll take hits in Iowa. - You can't criticize the mission.
我们需要你让大家保持平静
We need you to keep everyone calm.
你知道我对不必要的军事干涉的看法
You know how I feel about unnecessary military involvement.
是你要求做竞选搭档的  杰姬
You asked to be on the ticket, Jackie.
而你从一开始就各种不配合
It's been non-stop resistance from the start.
如果你不能支持总统
If you don't want to support the president,
那你就不该做他的副总统
you shouldn't want to be his number two.
我受够跟你扯皮了
I'm sick of pulling teeth.
你说得对  我会尽力的
You're right. I'll do what I can.
杰姬
Jackie...
我不是故意发火的
I didn't mean to snap.
我知道一边在这边保持影响力
I know it's hard having a presence here
一边竞选是很难的
and campaigning at the same time.
艾伦和孩子们肯定也不好受
I'm sure it's tough on Alan and the kids, too.
其实艾伦帮助很大
Alan's been a big help, actually.
我很高兴他在你需要的时候能支持你
I'm glad he's stepping up, giving you the support you need.
我还以为我会讨厌结婚
I thought I would hate it, the whole marriage thing.
结果还不错
But it's nice.
我能回家时  大家都围在桌旁
When I can get home, everyone around the table.
我有时甚至还做饭
I even cook sometimes.
-很难吃  他们都不忍心说  -不会吧
- Badly, but they indulge me. - No.
-我也有贤惠的一面  -穿围裙什么的吗
- I have my June Cleaver moments. - Apron and all?
别闹
Don't push it.
我记不得上次在家做饭吃是什么时候了
I can't remember the last time I had a home-cooked meal.
-会议要开始了  -是啊
- Session's about to start. - Yeah.
有消息我通知你
I'll fill you in after.
汤姆
Tom.
-你这一天干什么去了  -抱歉  写书呢
- Where have you been all day? - Sorry. Working on the book.
我知道我们本该找机会谈谈的
I know we were supposed to have an opportunity to speak,
-但现在的情况显然...  -当然
- but obviously now, it's-- - Of course.
你如果想到前面去  尽管去
Listen, you can come up and sit up front if you like.
-我和克莱尔谈过了  -后面挺好  谢谢
- I spoke to Claire about it. - I'm fine back here. Thanks.
那好
Okay.
我需要知道我的护照就要解锁了
I need to know this passport lock is being lifted.
先让我看看你的进展
Show me what you got.
我受够被人牵着鼻子走了
I'm tired of being strung along.
-有地点吗  -有  但我要知道还得多久
- You have a location? - Yeah. But I want a timeline.
-一两周吧  -不行
- Week or two. - No.
他们已经不再给我分配任务了
They've stopped giving me new assignments.
这意味着他们要动手收拾我了
That means they're getting ready to fuck me.
你必须再快点
It has to happen sooner than that.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
给国安部的朋友发邮件
E-mailing a friend in Homeland.
他回复我一向很快
He always gets back to me quickly.
满意了吗
You satisfied?
瑞秋
Rachel.
-这上面说无名女  -不  就是她
- It says Jane Doe. - No, it's her.
就是她
It's her.
她偷了一个叫丽贝卡·桑兹的女孩的身份
She ghosted the identity of a girl named Rebecca Sands.
生日很接近
The birthday's pretty close.
1990年8月  然后她93年就死了
It's August 1990, then she died in '93,
全家身亡
along with her whole family.
但她的社保号码6个月前被激活了
But her social went active about six months ago.
但这上面没写丽贝卡·桑兹  写的是无名女
But this doesn't say Rebecca Sands. It says Jane Doe.
州警在水沟里发现了她的尸体
State troopers found her body in a ditch,
就在图森市外的一个废弃建筑工地上
in an abandoned construction site outside of Tucson.
你这  连张照片都没有
I mean, there's no-- There's no picture.
什么都证明不了
There's no proof of anything.
"并且不要叫神的圣灵忧愁
"And do not grieve the Holy Spirit of God
你们原是受了他的印记  等候得赎的日子来到
by whom you were sealed for the day of redemption.
一切苦毒  恼恨  忿怒  喧嚷
Let all bitterness and wrath and anger
毁谤  同一切的恶毒  都要从你们中间除掉"
and clamor and evil speaking be put away from you."
不
No.
-不  不  这不是她  -指纹都有
- No, no. That's not her. - Come on, man. There's fingerprints.
这是你给我的那本《双城记》上面的指纹
Fingerprints from the Tale of Two Cities book that you gave me.
我和验尸报告比对过了
I ran it against the autopsy report.
和这位无名女完全吻合
It was a ten-point match with Jane Doe.
马上给我解锁护照
I need the passport lock lifted now.
-我会办的  -什么时候办
- I'm on it. - When will you be on it?
-尽快  -尽快是多快
- Soon. - Soon? How soon?
有多快是多快
As soon as I can!
我履行了约定  给我解锁护照
I did my part. Get the lock lifted.
这是赛斯·格雷森的号码
You've reached Seth Grayson.
有事请留言  我会尽快回复
Leave a message, I'll get back to you.
我得见他
I need to see him.
我母亲去世了
My mother died.
辛西娅/邓巴
拜托
Come on!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
伙计  你怎么回事
Hey, man. What the fuck?
对不起
Sorry.
简直难以置信
You believe this guy?
你是不是该和她说对不起  混蛋
You want to say it to her, shithead?
对不起  好吗  我很抱歉
Sorry. Okay, I'm sorry.
-我请你们喝酒  -我们不用你请  混蛋
- Drinks on me. - We don't want drinks, shithead.
你得走了  汤米  这家伙喝醉了
You need to get out of here. Tommy, this guy's trashed.
给  我请你们喝酒
Here. Drinks on me.
不不  我们不想喝酒  我们希望你离开
No, no. We don't want drinks. We want you to leave.
别这样  拿着吧  我都说对不起了
Come on. Just take it. I said I was sorry.
-我才不管  -拿着吧
- I don't give a shit. - Take it.
不行  他得道歉
No, he's apologizing. I'm telling you.
对不起
Sorry.
-对不起  对不起  对不起  -我打烂你脸
- Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! - I will bust your fucking face!
-冷静一下  我给你叫辆出租车  -好吧
- Calm down. Let me get you a cab. - Okay.
大家好  恐怕我没有什么新消息
Hello, everyone. I'm afraid I don't have much news.
我们已经和俄国取得了联系
We are in touch, uh, with the Russians,
但了解到的细节还很少
but there's very few details.
我正在等待与佩特罗夫总统通话
I'm waiting to speak with President Petrov.
-为什么耽搁至今  -他刚失去八名士兵
- Any reason for the delay? - He just lost eight soldiers.
他现在首先要和他们的家人谈话
Talking to their families is his priority
换做是我也会这样做
as it would be mine.
您认为这会危及到维和任务吗
Do you think this could jeopardize the peacekeeping mission?
每个派出部队的国家
Well, every country that contributed troops
都明白这样的事可能发生
knew that something like this was a possibility.
但俄国当初很反对这个计划
But the Russians fought this plan hard.
这给了佩特罗夫完美的撤兵借口
This gives Petrov the perfect out.
我不会妄加揣测佩特罗夫总统的想法
I wouldn't presume to know what President Petrov is thinking.
等我们有机会谈过以后我会知道更多
I'll know more once we have a chance to speak.
那么国会呢  他们当初也不支持这项任务
What about Congress? They weren't fans of this mission.
我们一回去  我就会和国会领导层
I'm gonna consult with congressional leadership
进行讨论
as soon as we get back.
与此同时  我主要
In the meantime, my focus
要尽我所能帮助俄国人
is to help the Russians in any way that I can.
他们不许任何人接近爆炸地点  你怎么能帮他们
How can you help them when they won't let anyone near the blast site?
这种说法还没得到确认
Well, that hasn't been confirmed.
当然  除非
Unless, of course,
你的情报来源比五角大楼还好
you have better intelligence than the Pentagon.
非常感谢大家  很快会有更多消息
Thank you all very much. More soon.
以色列想要公开指责巴勒斯坦应为攻击负责
Israel wants to go public, blame Palestine for the attack.
目前还没有证据呢
There's no evidence yet.
是的  他们要说的是
Yes, well, the message is that
巴勒斯坦应该管好自己国家的人民
Palestine should be keeping its people in check.
他们还从贝特谢安派出500名士兵
They've also moved 500 troops to a staging area
跨过边境去一处集结待命区
across the border from Beit She'an.
老天啊  再打给克里姆林宫试试
Christ. Try the Kremlin again, please.
打个哈欠提提神吧
You try yawning?
那对你管用  对我不管用
That works for you, not for me.
那喝点水呢  有时能有用
What about some water? Sometimes that helps.
我不需要喝水  我需要接通电话
I don't need water, I need a phone call.
你等电话的时候
Maybe you should talk to Traub
或许该和特劳伯谈谈
while you're waiting for that phone call.
-你不吃点吗  -我不饿
- You're not eating? - I'm not hungry.
我觉得你是不喜欢坐飞机
I think you don't like to fly.
把桌子当脱衣舞女的奶头一样抓得紧紧的
Holding onto that table like it's a stripper's tits.
哈兰  很抱歉让你久等了
Harlan. I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
不必起身  龙虾味道如何
Please, don't get up. How's your lobster?
像今天早晨刚抓的一样新鲜
It tastes like it was caught this morning.
确实是刚抓的  空军一号一切都是最好的
Well, it was. Nothing but the best for Air Force One.
先生  我知道您现在有很多事要考虑
Sir, I know you have a million things on your mind,
但我非常想与您讨论一下如何推进
but I would just love to talk to you about how to modernize
爱荷华食品加工业的现代化进程
the food-processing industry in Iowa.
拜托  用他的餐刀杀了我算了
Please, slit my wrists with his butter knife.
我们不能在飞机上讨论大选  哈兰
We can't talk election on the plane, Harlan.
这是选举委员会严格禁止的
That's an FEC no-no.
这与竞选无关
This isn't about the campaign.
我们在谈论经济而不是党团会议  对吗  哈兰
We're talking about the economy, not the caucus. Right, Harlan?
十分正确
That's right.
相信您知道  先生  我们在玉米和大豆
I'm sure you're aware, sir, that we lead the states
生产上都领先各州
in corn and soybean production.
考虑到素食主义的流行  这是件好事
It's a good thing, given the trend towards vegan.
但我们的食品加工厂
But our food-processing plants--
-爱荷华最大的产业  -没错
- Well, the largest industry in Iowa. - That's correct.
他们渐渐赶不上时代了  先生
And they're slow on the uptake, sir.
我们需要联邦政府的拨款
We need federal funding to help subsidize
-资助转向更健康的...  -总统先生
- the transition toward healthier-- - Mr. President.
俄罗斯来电
our call from Russia.
非常抱歉  我得接这个电话
Oh. I'm so sorry. I have to take this.
但是哈兰  我们回头一定好好谈  我保证
But Harlan, we'll get into it, I promise.
维克多  真是可怕的惨剧  总统先生
Viktor, it's a terrible tragedy, Mr. President.
我深感同情
I feel for your loss.
这就是你们的人一直打个不停的原因吗
This is why your people were so persistent?
就为了让你表示哀悼吗
So you could offer your sympathy?
我们必须得沟通
It's important that we talk.
你不让任何人接近爆炸地点
You're not letting anyone near the blast site.
我们在自己进行调查
We're conducting our investigation.
让联合国调查员和你们一起调查
Well, is there anything wrong with allowing UN investigators
有什么不妥吗
to work in conjunction with your people?
联合国指挥官派我的人
UN Command sent my men on that patrol,
去整个河谷90号公路最危险的一段巡逻
the most dangerous stretch of Route 90 in the entire valley.
-是你派我的人去的  -我吗  你在说什么
- And you sent my men. - Me? What are you talking about?
你觉得我的人无关紧要
You saw my men as expendable.
维克多  维和部队不归我个人管
Viktor, I don't personally oversee the peacekeeping forces,
你不会真觉得
and you can't possibly think
把你的人派到危险地段
that there was some deliberate attempt
-是有意而为的吧  -不然我该怎么想
- to put your men in harm's way. - So I am to believe, what?
这是个巧合吗
That this was a random act of fate, yes?
听着  不管责任在谁
Listen, whoever's responsible,
我们不能让这件事离间我们的关系
we can't let them foment distrust between us.
我们要是不和  就正中他们下怀了
If we do, then they win.
让他们看到  意外让我们更团结
Let's show them that an incident like this makes us stronger.
让我们帮你查出幕后黑手
Let us help you find out who did this.
死的是俄罗斯人  俄罗斯会找出凶手
Russians are dead. Russia will find the killers.
我不明白你为什么拒绝我们的帮助
I don't understand why you're refusing our assistance.
因为我们不需要
Because we don't need it.
那我们能不能至少保持沟通
Well, can we at least keep the dialogue open?
在进行任何行动前互相商讨一下
Consult with each other before you make any move?
我要做我必须做的  总统先生
I'm going to do what I must, Mr. President.
维克多  请听我说  我们得
Viktor, please listen to me. We have--
对不起  总统先生  线路挂断了
I'm sorry, Mr. President, but the line has been disconnected.
他挂我电话
He hung up on me.
帮我接凯茜·杜兰特
Cathy Durant, please.
鲍德温说得没错
Baldwin was right.
死去的八名战士给了佩特罗夫一个借口
Those eight bodies give Petrov options.
他才没有潸然泪下  他在开香槟庆祝呢
He's not shedding tears, he's popping champagne corks.
我能听到
I can hear them.
不在这儿  先生  卫生间在这边
Not here. Sir. Restroom's this way.
刚那是谁  刚进来的那人是谁
Who was that? The guy who just came in?
没看到
Didn't see him.
我可以到你办公室去
I would've come to your office.
这是联合国唯一一间俄国没有监控的房间
This is the only room at the UN we don't monitor.
-我想你们也没有监控  -没  美国也没有
- I'm assuming you don't either. - No, we haven't bugged it.
-那我们能打开天窗说亮话了  -也该说了
- So we can speak openly. - I think we should.
你说  我听着
You talk. I'll listen.
巴勒斯坦说如果以色列军队进入河谷
Palestine says it can't control Hamas
他们控制不了哈马斯
if Israeli troops cross into the valley.
我们只能私下沟通  亚历克西
We have to back channel this, Alexi.
佩特罗夫不肯听弗兰西斯的
Petrov won't listen to Francis.
亚历克西  这事你不能坐视不管
Alexi, please. This whole thing, you can't let it devolve
让事态完全失控
into something nobody can control.
也许这就是目的所在
Well, maybe that was the objective.
什么目的
What was?
总统本来就反对这次维和任务
The President... never wanted the peacekeeping mission.
你刚说"目的"
You said "Objective."
你是说这都是计划好的吗
Are you telling me this was somehow planned?
我什么都没说
I haven't said anything.
但你想说
But you want to.
全世界都想知道这件事是谁干的
The whole world wants to know who is responsible.
你们的军队不让任何人进入爆炸地点
Your troops won't let anyone near the blast site.
因为他们不想让世人知道真相
Because they don't want the world to know.
我弟弟  他在俄罗斯联邦安全局
My brother... he's in the FSB.
我们一周前还说过话  那之后就没了音讯
We spoke a week ago. I haven't heard from him since.
你万分确定吗
Are you absolutely certain about this?
亚历克西  公开吧
Alexi, go public.
我们会庇护你的
We'll protect you.
就像你们庇护冯山德那样吗
Like you did Xander Feng?
这是两码事
That was different.
我还有家庭
I have a family.
俄联邦安全局以前也干过这种事
The FSB has conducted these sorts of operations before.
公寓被炸事件
The apartment complex that blew up,
1999年9月
莫斯科等城市发生多起公寓被炸案
俄罗斯指责是车臣叛军所为
车臣叛军则指控是俄秘密部门所为
成了佩特罗夫用来进攻车臣的理由
Petrov used that to justify invading Chechnya.
剧院毒气事件
The opera house that was gassed,
2002年10月23至26日
俄突击队冲入莫斯科一家戏院
营救被车臣叛军扣压的七百名俄国人质
最终129名人质死亡
41名车臣叛军被击毙
多数人死于未知毒气
那之后他换掉了所有省长
he removed all provincial governors after that.
我们的确认为第一件事与俄联邦安全局有关
We do believe the FSB participated in the first.
剧院事件我们仍不确定
We're still uncertain about the opera house.
但炸死他自己的士兵
But blowing up his own soldiers,
我还是觉得难以置信
I find that very difficult to believe.
他直截了当地说了吗  他说出口了吗
Did he tell you point blank? Did he say the words?
他把能说的都说了
He said as much as he could.
但他的暗示很明确
But the implication was crystal clear.
我相信他一定很令人信服
I'm sure he was very convincing.
俄国所有外交官都经过了
All Russian diplomats go through
俄联邦安全局的反情报训练
FSB counter-intel training.
他们想刺激我们做出行动
They're trying to provoke some sort of reaction out of us.
那他弟弟呢
But what about his brother?
他弟弟确实是在俄联邦安全局工作
It is true that his brother works for the FSB,
我们也的确上周后就找不到他了
and that we lost track of him last week.
这部分属实
That part of the story holds up.
我们对莫里科夫有什么了解
What's our profile on Moryakov?
我们有特工调查过他  先生  吉姆
We have our agent who's been assigned to him, sir. Jim?
莫斯科认为莫里科夫有点捉摸不定
Moryakov has been considered a bit of a wild card in Moscow.
佩特罗夫曾两次考虑将他召回
Petrov considered recalling him twice,
但碍于和他父亲的交情就不了了之
but held off because his father's a family friend.
这几个月来我们收集到些只言片语
Now, we picked up some chatter in recent months,
他对克林姆林宫处理约旦河谷问题的方式有所担忧
his misgivings with how the Kremlin's been handling the Jordan Valley.
但你觉得他会做叛徒吗
But does he strike you as a traitor?
他很难说  他极度民族主义
He's a complicated man. Fiercely nationalistic.
但他对佩特罗夫绝对有疑虑
But he definitely has doubts about Petrov.
我们至少该考虑一下这种可能吧
Shouldn't we at least entertain the possibility?
是啊  但我们怎么确定
Yeah, but how can we determine it
到底是怎么样的  如何确认
one way or the other? Definitively?
光靠卫星不够
Our satellites aren't enough.
我们得派人去爆炸地点
We'd have to get men to the blast site,
采集土壤样本和爆炸残片
retrieve soil samples and blast debris.
我们多快能派人过去
How soon could we get a team in?
72小时吧
I'd estimate 72 hours.
三天也太久了
Well, three days seems an awfully long time.
调派的基本准备不是已经就绪了吗
Don't we already have the basics in place for deployment?
但那没有考虑应对俄罗斯军队
That doesn't take into account the Russian forces.
我们想在出兵之前掌握更多情报
We'd want better intel before deploying.
那是不是随着时间推移
Am I correct in assuming that every hour that passes,
我们获取证据的几率也在降低
our chances of retrieving any proof diminish?
是的  先生
That is correct, sir.
那调派最快需要多久
What's the absolute soonest you can deploy?
12小时  总统先生
Twelve hours, Mr. President.
但这样就有极高的...
But that would involve an extremely high degree--
我知道有风险  上将
Yeah, I'm aware of the risk, Admiral.
胜算有多大
What are the odds of success?
说实话  先生  没有准确情报
Honestly, sir, without proper intelligence,
我最多只能说一半一半
I can't say better than 50/50.
你确定吗
You're certain?
我确定
Yes, I am.
那就准备行动
Let's put it in motion.
-总统先生  -马克
- Mr. President? - Mark.
不是应该联合国去调查
Shouldn't the UN be conducting the investigation
而不是俄罗斯吗
instead of the Russians?
俄罗斯在此次行动之初
The Russians have been our partners
就是我们的合作伙伴
in this mission from day one of deployment,
所以我认为他们是代表联合国进行自主调查
so I would say that they're conducting their own investigation on behalf
而不是取代联合国
of the United Nations, not instead of.
-总统先生  -萨拉
- Mr. President? - Sara.
那是不是说
Is it correct to say that
他们不会向联合国指挥部汇报
they are in no way reporting to UN Command?
在维和任务中  每个国家志愿派遣军力
In peacekeeping missions, nations volunteer their forces.
他们首先是听命于本国政府
They answer to their own governments first and foremost,
其次再是与联合国指挥部合作
then they cooperate with the UN Command.
两者有重要区别
That's an important distinction to make.
其他关于约旦河谷的问题
Now, any other questions with respect to the Jordan Valley
都请向国务院提出
should be directed to the State Department.
如果还有跟昨天的事
But if any of you have questions
无关的问题
that don't relate to yesterday's events,
我可以回答一下  斯黛芬妮
I'll take one or two. Yeah, Stephanie.
总统先生  我跟凯特都有个问题
Mr. President, Kate and I both had a question.
谢谢  斯黛芬妮
Thank you, Stephanie.
总统先生  您知道
Mr. President, are you aware, sir,
在空军一号上进行竞选活动
that campaigning on Air Force One
-是违反选举委员会规定的吗  -我知道
- is a violation of FEC rules? - Yes, in general, I am.
昨天哈兰·特劳伯也在飞机上
Harlan Traub was on the plane yesterday.
他出现在那儿的原因
It's hard to imagine he was there
大概只能是你在寻求他在爱荷华州的支持吧
for any other reason than you'd be seeking his support in Iowa.
你不知道  我跟他是老交情了
You don't know how long I've known him,
他昨天的确在飞机上
and yes, he was on the plane yesterday.
但我没进行选举活动就不算违规
But it's not a violation if you don't campaign, which I didn't.
我也就问了问
I think the extent of our conversation
他吃得怎么样
was asking him how he liked his meal.
不过我乐意接受选举委员会的裁决
But I'm happy to let the FEC decide.
还有谁要受人所托
Now, does anybody else have any question
问我什么问题吗
that somebody else asked them to ask me?
特劳伯呢
Where's Traub now?
酒店里  一小时内能到
At the Hay-Adams. Should be here in an hour.
被人看见他在白宫不好吧
It'd be bad if anyone saw him at the White House.
我现在都不想让他来首都
Well, I don't even want him in DC now.
我得处理俄罗斯的问题
The last thing we need is some bullshit FEC story
不能再让选举委员会找上茬
while I'm trying to deal with the Russians.
送他回爱荷华吧  你来处理
Let's get him back to Iowa. And you handle this.
你比沃恩更擅长与人打交道
You have better people skills than Vaughn.
你跟鲍德温谈
And you talk to Baldwin.
跟她说明白我们没违反任何规定
You make it crystal clear we violated no regulations.
先生  道格昨晚给我留言了
Sir? I got a voicemail from Doug last night.
-他说他母亲去世了  -真糟糕
- He said his mom died. - My God, that's awful.
可是茱莉亚·斯坦普十年前就去世了
Except Julia Stamper passed away ten years ago.
我知道  我去了葬礼
I know, I was at the funeral.
送些花吧  把道格请来吧
Send some flowers. Actually, get Doug in here.
我想亲自表示哀悼
I'd like to give my condolences in person.
通过《美国就业法案》
There's a whole host of ways
我们有很多在爱荷华州
we can revolutionize food processing in Iowa
革新食品加工业的办法
through America Works.
你们研发需要的补贴
The subsidies you want for R and D
-可以当作...  -你不用这样的
- can be financed as a jobs-- - You don't have to do this.
-哪样  -跟我说好话
- Do what? - Sweet talk me.
给我叫辆车就可以了
And a cab would've been fine.
我想亲自开车送你去机场
I wanted to drive to the airport myself
好聊聊  谈谈你的顾虑
so we had a chance to talk about your concerns.
我都跟候选人聊  不是司机
Well, I'm used to talking to candidates, not chauffeurs.
我不是司机
I'm not a chauffeur.
你不是开着车吗
Well, it's your hands on the wheel.
赛斯
Seth?
该死
Shit.
请出示车辆登记和保险证明
Registration and insurance, please.
抱歉  警官  钱包落在办公室了
I'm sorry, officer. I left my wallet at work.
车辆登记  保险证明呢
Registration? Proof of insurance?
-在钱包里  -应该放在车上的
- In my wallet. - You're supposed to keep it in the car.
是啊  但要是车被偷了  手续不也没了
Yeah. But if someone steals your car, why give 'em the paperwork?
好吧
All right,
请你下车吧  先生
I'm gonna need you to step out of the car for a moment, please.
警官  我是雷米·丹顿
Officer, my name is Remy Danton.
总统的幕僚长
I'm Chief of Staff to the president.
不出示证件的话  我也不知道你是谁  先生
Without your identification, sir, I don't know who you are.
-我有白宫的胸针  -那也没用  先生
- Got my government pin. - That doesn't matter, sir.
还是要出示证件
I still need to see your identification.
请下车吧
Would you step out of the car, please?
警官  搜一下雷米·丹顿  能搜到我的照片
Officer, you run a search on Remy Danton, you'll get my photo.
先生  请下车
Sir, I asked you to step out of the car. Please.
-带武器了吗  -当然没有
- Any weapons on you? - Of course not.
好  请站到车辆后方
All right. You mind stepping to the rear of the vehicle, please?
为了保险  我还是要搜一下
I'm gonna pat you down, just to make sure.
脚往后站
Feet back.
车是登记在一个弗吉尼亚州企业名下  没有地址
Car comes back to a Virginia corporation, no address.
我接触机密信息  身份自然是保密的
I'm cleared Top Secret, my information is masked.
先生  请你在这儿等一下
Sir, I need you to stay here for a moment, please.
-查到什么了  -没有地址
- What do you got? - No address on file.
-为什么拦下我  -稍等  先生
- Why'd you stop me? - One moment, sir.
不  别敷衍我
No, not one moment.
我有权知道你们为什么让我停车
I got the right to know why you stopped me.
先生  请你把手放在车上
Sir, I asked you to keep your hands on the car.
把你的警号告诉我
I'm gonna need your badge number.
想向你搭档炫耀吗  伙计
Trying to show off for your partner here, brother?
别叫我伙计  别逼我们拷你
I'm not your brother. Don't make us restrain you.
-戴维斯警官  -先生
- Officer Davis. - Sir.
柯克兰警官
Officer Corchoran.
这么着吧  我要照张照片
Know what? I'm gonna take a photo.
搞什么
What the fuck?!
-你们搞什么  -冷静点
- What's your problem?! - Calm down!
先生
Sir!
把你的警号给我
I'm gonna need your badge number!
丹顿先生  我是希克森副队长
Mr. Danton, I'm Lieutenant Hixson.
我为此次误会向您道歉
I'm very sorry for this misunderstanding.
小心别撞头
Watch your head.
我代表他们向您道歉  希望您能接受
I hope you accept my apology on their behalf.
-他们说让我停车是因为超速  -对
- They said I was stopped for speeding. - Yes.
当驾驶员无法出示驾照和车辆登记的时候...
When they encounter someone without a license and registration--
开罚单
Write up the ticket.
不用担心这个  先生  您可以走了
You don't have to worry about that, sir. You're free to go.
如果我当时超速了  就给我开罚单
If I was speeding, give me the damn ticket.
让您遭了这番罪  真的没这必要了
That's really not necessary after everything we put you through.
副队长
Lieutenant.
我也想请你上去  但孩子们
I'd invite you up, but the kids, they're--
我们准备这次带他们一起去爱荷华
We're bringing them to Iowa this trip
简直乱套了
and it's a total shit-show.
我来不是为了竞选的事
I didn't come here to talk to you about the campaign.
我可能...
I probably... you know,
我不该就这样跑来  但...
I shouldn't have just shown up like this, but...
来  到这边来
Here. Come this way.
真是丢人  我都不知道我为什么来
It's stupid. I don't even know why I came over.
发生什么事了吗
Did something happen?
我开车时  因为超速被警察拦下
I got pulled over. For speeding.
事情有点失控  开着豪车的黑鬼
Things got out of hand. A nigger in a nice car.
老天
Jesus.
我把钱包落在办公室了
I left my wallet at work.
我告诉他我是谁
When I tried to tell the guy who I was,
他却根本不相信
he didn't believe me, so...
我说不清
I don't know.
我也不相信我自己
I didn't believe me.
我手被铐住时就好像
There I was with my hands in cuffs and it was like, uh...
我根本不是我自己
it was like I was outside of myself.
我可能是任何人
I could've been anyone.
但就不是我自己
I wasn't me.
-这么说你能明白吗  -你只是吓坏了
- Does that make any sense? - You got rattled.
不  不是那样
No, it's not that.
我看你和艾伦  甚至是弗兰克和克莱尔
I look at you and Alan, and even Frank and Claire.
发生这种事我连个倾诉对象都没有
This happened and I didn't have anyone to tell about it.
你有我呢
You have me, right?
你来我很开心
I'm glad you came over.
这不公平  这样打扰你
It's not fair. Intruding on you like this.
如果我认为你这是打扰  我根本就不会下来
If I thought you were intruding, I wouldn't have come downstairs.
我很抱歉  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我
I--
你对我仍然很重要
You still mean a lot to me.
作为朋友  我会扶持你
I am there for you, as your friend.
你该回去了  继续打包
You should go back up. Finish packing.
一路平安
Safe flight.
我们准备在东部时间晚上9点
We're set to insert at 2100 EST,
当地时间凌晨4点空降
0400 local time.
我们将使用富尔顿地对空回收系统
We'll use a Fulton recovery
收集所有材料样品
of any material samples.
如何撤出呢
The extraction?
小队将步行前往
The team will make its way on foot
这个指定地点等待撤离
to this rendezvous point for extract.
他们要怎样穿过俄罗斯的防线
How are they gonna pass the Russian lines?
我们的情报有限  但小队将和
Our intel is spotty at best, but our team is scheduled
当地协助行动的特工汇合
to link up with a local agent who will assist.
我们去战况室继续谈
All right. Let's move this down to the Situation Room.
我几分钟后到
I'll be there in a few minutes.
-是  长官  -是  长官
- Yes, Sir. - Yes, Sir.
他说什么了吗
Did he say anything?
我打招呼的时候他看都没看我
He wouldn't even look at me when I said hello.
让他进来
Send him in.
道格
Doug.
你确定吗
Are you certain?
这些信息是谁收集的...算了  不该问的
Who gathered all this inform-- Oh, never mind. I shouldn't know.
是你  把她...
Was it you... who...?
不是
No.
不该带到这儿来
You shouldn't have brought this here.
我想要你看看
I wanted you to see it.
好让你相信我
So you would believe me.
真残酷
Brutal.
我醉了  先生
I'm drunk, sir.
我现在还醉着
I'm-- I'm drunk right now.
你真的很在意这姑娘  是吧
This girl really meant something to you, didn't she?
是啊
Yeah.
没错
She did.
我在给邓巴工作
I've been working for Dunbar.
我把自己逼得太狠了  是我的错
I pushed myself too much. It's my fault.
我是为了你  看看自己能走到哪一步
It was for you. To see how close I could get.
看能不能找到什么致命信息
If I could find something, a silver bullet.
证明自己的价值
To prove that... I was still useful.
需要我帮忙吗  道格
How can I help you, Doug?
我不想去戒酒中心
I can't go to rehab.
-别送我去医院或是...  -好
- Just not another hospital, or... - Okay.
我就是  真的撑不住
I just... I can't... I can't do it.
我们再想办法
We'll figure something out.
我不是彼得·罗素
I'm not Peter Russo.
我不会跟他一个下场
I won't go like he did.
当然不会  你会好起来的  道格
No, you won't. You're going to get better, Doug.
我保证
I promise you that.
叫密查姆进来
Yes, send Meechum in here.
我桌上有个信封  需要烧毁
There's an envelope on my desk. I need it to be incinerated.
好的
Yes, sir.
然后送道格回家
And then I need you to take Doug home.
走吧  道格  该走了
Come on, Doug, it's time to go.
这边  斯坦普先生
This way, Mr. Stamper.
你先陪着他  我们再作打算
You stay with him until we figure out what's next.
好的
Yes, sir.
请出去一下
Some privacy, please.
-我是希瑟·邓巴  -马上给您接通
- This is Heather Dunbar. - I'll connect you momentarily.
希瑟
Heather?
总统先生
Mr. President?
道格·斯坦普是我的朋友
Doug Stamper is my friend,
你差一点把他害死
and you came very close to killing him.
-什么  -你知道他以前酗酒吧
- Excuse me? - You're aware he's an alcoholic?
-知道  -以及他伤得多严重
- Yes. - And how serious his injuries were.
-总统先生...  -但你还是让他工作
- Mr. President-- - But you still put him to work.
让一个康复中  想回到正轨上的人工作
A man who's trying to recover, who's trying to get back his life.
你真觉得他能应付得了吗
Did you honestly think that he could handle that?
是道格拉斯来找我们的
Douglas came to us.
你要是还要脸就该拒绝他
And you should've turned him away if you had one ounce of decency.
怎么了  他没事吧
What's happened? Is he okay?
你没权利问我这个
You don't have the right to ask me that question.
你要是再做威胁他健康的事
And if you do anything that endangers his health again,
我对天发誓
I swear to God,
我一定要了你的命
I will put you in your fucking grave.
继续谈吧
Let's continue.
3.2万英尺  一分钟后跳伞
Thirty-two thousand feet, one minute to insert.
接通无线电
Let's hear comms.
打开音频
Audio on.
起立
Stand up!
20秒  最后检查一遍
Twenty seconds. Last checks.
最后检查  过来
Last checks! Gather round.
十秒  九  八  七
Ten seconds. Nine, eight, seven,
六  五  四
six, five, four,
三  二  行动
three, two. Green light.
-跳后会失去视频信号  -跳  跳
- Video will go dark once they jump. - Go. Go.
降落伞已打开
Chutes deployed.
集结点
The rally point.
和当地特工在这里会合
Link-up with indig agent happens here,
离降落地点五百米
half a klick from the drop zone.
他会带路进入爆炸现场
He'll arrange safe passage to the blast site.
我操
Motherfucker!
特工反水  重复  特工反水
Agent is rogue. Repeat, we have a bad agent.
-我们暴露了  -有人倒下  有人倒下
- We've been compromised. - Man down! Man down!
-操  -这边
- Fuck. - Over there!
-特工已击毙  -按住伤口
- Agent is kilo. - Get pressure on that wound.
该放弃了  先生
We should abort, sir.
-总统先生  -终止行动  让他们回来
- Mr. President. - Shut it down. Bring them home.
"火柴棍"  重复  "火柴棍"
"Match Stick," I repeat, "Match Stick."
直接前往X地点  收到吗
Head directly to waypoint X-ray. How copy, over?
前往X地点
Proceeding to X-ray.
-有人吗  -他在卧室
- Hello? - He's in the bedroom.
好啊  弟弟
Hey, brother.
请重复  完毕
Say again. Over.
已确认  长官
Confirmed, sir.
已离开X地点  前往撤离点
The element is off the X and moving to extract.
三人受伤  一人身亡
Three wounded, one KIA.
给我名字  亲属
I'll need the name, next of kin.
好的
Yes, sir.
怎么了
Yes?
先生  佩特罗夫总统来电
Sir, President Petrov is on the line.
我在这儿接  请关上门
I'll take it in here. Shut the door, please.
-维克多  -我们知道是你的人
- Viktor. - We know it was your men.
什么
What was?
你以为我们发现不了吗
Did you think we wouldn't detect you?
不管你说的是什么  我都不知情
Whatever you're accusing us of, I don't know anything about it.
你当然知道  以色列人也知道了
Oh, yes, you do. And so do the Israelis.
我们把交火录像泄露给他们了
We leaked footage of the firefight to them.
听到美国绕过他们
I can't imagine they'd be pleased
执行机密行动  他们不会开心吧
America is conducting covert operations without consulting with them first.
你杀了自己的士兵  维克多
You killed your own men, Viktor.
昨晚中枪的是你的人
It was your man who got shot last night.
我指爆炸  我们有情报
I mean the blast. We have the intel.
是你  不是恐怖分子  是俄安全局
It was you, not terrorists. It was FSB.
你在华盛顿羞辱我  在莫斯科羞辱我
So you humiliate me in Washington, humiliate me in Moscow,
如今还要用你荒唐的幻想羞辱我吗
and now you insult me with these ridiculous fantasies.
你搞这一切想要什么  维克多
What do you want out of all of this, Viktor?
正义  我的士兵在你发起的行动中丧生了
Justice, for my soldiers who died on a mission you devised.
他们的死只能怪你
If anyone is to blame for their deaths, it's you.
再见  维克多
Goodbye, Viktor.
弗兰西斯  他说什么了
Francis, what did he say?
我得写完这封信
I have to finish this letter.
过去数小时内
Over the last several hours,
以色列军队进入了约旦河谷
Israeli forces entered the Jordan Valley.
以军进入约旦河谷
有目击者称
Eyewitness reports say
他们驻扎营地的地方
they've taken up positions near the encampments
就在俄军的爆炸现场封锁线旁
where Russian troops are refusing access to a blast site
也是八名俄罗斯士兵丧生的地方
where eight of their countrymen were killed two days ago.
以色列总理说
The Israeli Prime Minister had this to say, quote:
"俄方拒绝撤军
"With both Russian forces refusing to leave
又有他国展开机密行动..."
and the presence of covert operations from other nations..."
哈马斯和黎巴嫩真主党要插手了
Hamas and Hezbollah are getting involved.
为什么
How?
他们曾宣称  如果以军过境就召集当地武装
They've vowed to raise local militias if the Israelis cross the border.
美方政府也未就机密行动一事发表声明
...nor has the American government regarding covert operations.
-这事可大了  -是啊
- This is gonna be bad. - Yeah, it sure is.
我得去白宫了
I should get to the White House.
出去时记得锁门
Lock the door on the way out?
以色列人
The Israelis.
我知道  我整晚都在看新闻
I know, I've been watching the news all night.
该去战况室了
We should get to the Situation Room.
我先写完  马上下去
Let me finish this first. I'll be right down.
好  在那儿见
All right, I'll see you down there.
尼克斯先生  夫人
我怀着悲痛的心情通知你们
10月18日周日
你们的儿子在演练中不幸丧生
我的悲痛无以言表...
弗兰西斯·J·安德伍德
对于每一位美国总统来说
下达命令派出特种部队执行危险任务  都是一种赌博
在战场上  没有任何任务能够保证百分百成功
美军历史上有多次特殊任务惨败的教训
在讨论是否派出特种部队猎杀本·拉登时
经验丰富的前国防部长盖茨建议采取轰炸的方式  而不是派兵突袭
奥巴马最后决定派出最精良的海豹特工六队
但是出发前白宫和五角大楼都没有百分百的成功把握
幸运的是  虽然行动中美军损失了一架直升机
但是这次行动还是非常成功的
奥巴马的冒险也得到了政治上的巨大回报
在2012年的大选中  奥巴马一直拿猎杀拉登的行动
来证明自己在国家安全事务上卓有成效
但是白宫战况室里发出的命令  也有很多没有获得预期的成功
近来中东极端恐怖组织杀害了多名美国人质
悲剧发生后  美国军方向媒体吐露
奥巴马曾经下令特种部队对人质进行营救
但是由于情报等原因  营救行动均未成功